Tammam Mabroukeh

React JS Developer | Next JS Developer

As a Frontend web developer with expertise in React.js & Next.js, I am driven by my passion for designing appealing interfaces. I worked as a freelancer. I have honed my programming skills in languages like JavaScript and Typescript. My exceptional communication skills are an added asset to my profile.

Work Experience

Scripts Ocean, Turkey (May 2024 - Present) **Project Link**

Frontend Engineer - Part Time (Remote)

 Responsible for implementing the company's website using different technologies (Next.js 14 tailwindcss, nextui, next-auth, framer-motion. tabler/icons, next-safe-action, (is not finished)

White-soog, Jordan (Aug 2023 - Nov 2023) **Project Link**

Frontend Engineer - Full Time (Remote)

 I was responsible for building the company's website using React.js 18 library, MUI, Axios, context api, react-router-dom, react-slider ...) and integrate with Rest api.

Personal Projects

TSP Project (Apr 2024)

Project Link This project about the traveling salesman algorithm. The project takes

income from the user, representing the capacity of the trucks that will distribute the items and the value of each item, in addition to the city to which the item will go, as well as the distance between all cities, and then the algorithm distributes the trucks to the goods in the optimal way, using (Next.js, TailwindCss, typescript, react-hook-form, reactgraph-vis, flask, Rest api).

Netflix Website (Mar 2024)

A site similar to Netflix, where the user logs in using Google, GitHub, or email. It contains many movies, displaying the trailer and information for each movie, with the ability to add the movie to favorites and add it to the user list, using (Next.js, TailwindCss, shadon, prisma, supabase, next-auth, typescript).

Contact

- Syria , Damascus , Barza.
- (**1**) +(963) 932 444 357
- <u>tamammb367@gmail.com</u>
- in <u>LinkedIn</u> <u>Telegram</u>
- GitHub | WhatsApp My Portfolio

Working

I worked at Mad Solution company as Front-End React.js developer for 6 months.

I have worked at Scripts Ocean company as Front-End Next.js & React.js developer.

Programming Languages:

JavaScript: Intermediate (2 years)

TypeScript: Good (1 year)

Frameworks, and services:

Design:

nextui - shadcnui.

TailwindCss - toast.

React-Bootstrap.

Material ui - swiperJS.

tailwindui - Headlessui.

<u>blurhash</u> - <u>skeleton.</u>

lottie-files. - framer-motion

Logic:

Project Link

Next.is 14 - React 18.

Redux - Redux-Toolkit.

Redux-persist. - next-intl

<u>react-query</u> - <u>next-auth.</u>

<u>rtk-query</u> - <u>next-safe-action</u>

E-commerce Website (Aug 2023)

Project Link

An online store that contains many pages such as the products page and the search page in addition to the shopping cart using (React js, Sass, Redux, api).

(It needs a vpn)

Portfolio (2022)

Project Link

Project Link

A personal website that contains works, projects, and ways to communicate with the owner of the site using (React js, Css3, Bootstrap, EmailJS)

Crypto-currency Website (2022)

Project Link

Cryptocurrency website that contains an explanation of digital currencies, in addition to the currency search feature using (React js, Css3, Redux, Rabidapi, TailwindCss).

(It needs a vpn)

Courses

- -The complete guide of React.js development on Udemy.
- -pro-frontend-engineer-reactjs-typescript-redux on Udemy.
- -Many courses on YouTube.

Certificates

ICPC

I participated in the 2023 programming competition.

Education

Syrian virtual University(SVU) (2020 - present)

Bachelor of technology. Grade: 83% (Excellent).

Validation:

Formik - Yup.

zod - react-hook-form,

API:

<u>Axios</u> - <u>zod-fetcher</u>

Other:

<u>lucide-icons</u> - <u>heroicons</u>.

EmailJs,

Languages

Arabic: native

English: Intermediate

Core skills:

- React.js 18.
- Next.js 14.
- Node.js.

Tools:

- Git. Gitlab and Github.
- MySQL.
- json-server.
- Command Line.
- VS Code

Soft Skills:

- Problem solving
- Communication skills
- Time Management
- Teamwork skills
- Research
- Learning methods
- Prioritization